[{"answer": "No. Won't do it for less than twenty", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "All right... Where's, uh, where's your old lady at", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "But you know something", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Right Lite", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It helps if you dress like a detective, too. Detectives dress kind of square. People think this guy is a cop. They're going to think you're packing something. They don't fuck  with you so much", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Am I what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What, and lose my job? The law requires that I stay right here until you call my branch manager", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "That's the law", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "There's going to be some bad shit  coming down one of these days kid", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Ung Uh, I'm going to be right here heading north at a hundred and ten per", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Roll the window down", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A chingas tu esposa", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Pick it up! Look at you. You pick it up. You know yourself you were wrong", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "They weren't in the middle of the street. That not the middle of the street that's the corner", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Flying saucers. Which are really? Yeah you got it. Time machines. I think a lot about this kind of stuff. I do my best thinking on the bus. That how come I don't drive, see", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't want to know how. I don't want to learn. See? The more you drive, the less intelligent you are", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Any thing for you babes", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'll be right back", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Fuck you!  You little scumbag", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Don't you ever tell me to shut up", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What do you mean? Stolen", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Hot", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Jesus Christ.", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You repo men, you guys are all out to fuckin  lunch. Let's get out of here", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Huh? Why are you looking for the that place", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Illegal aliens", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Damn straight I do", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend who", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Not any more. We ate 'em", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You shut up", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Bullshit  you're taking their word against mine", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Take the rest of the? I can't take the rest of the...OW yeah! I Un Huh I get it. Take the flippin rest of the week off budsky. So you can get the flippin twenty thousand dollars for the that place", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yeah? Well fuck  you", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Great! I'll come back and pick up my stuff later when the fucking  place don't stink so bad", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "This is really a nice old car. Why don't you let me drive", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Well I don't know. I mean...uh! Don't you feel funny.", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Why should I feel funny? The two hemispheres are fundamentally at odds. Hemisphere, Hemisphere. You know it's strange. I do feel funny..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Hey ace. Wait up", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Talk about what kid", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend, my friend pull your self together", "docId": "Repo-Man.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "We're going to the hospital", "qsentId": 44}]